<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work Visa 482 | Finer Immigration Law Firm</title>
    <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Work Visa 482 | Finer Immigration Law Firm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 22:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>“No Further Stay” condition 8503  waiver under the coronavirus outbreak. </title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/visa-190-victoria-state-nominated-permanent-visa-opportunities-for-cook-baker-interpreter-chef-human-resources-manager-dietitian-etc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/visa-190-victoria-state-nominated-permanent-visa-opportunities-for-cook-baker-interpreter-chef-human-resources-manager-dietitian-etc/</guid>
      <description>The DoHA announced the flexible approach in order to deal with the dilemma amid coronavirus outbreak.
The Doha has advised temporary visa holders can apply for another visa to extend their stay in Australia if they are unable to travel. We understand that the current circumstance has left many temporary visa holders in Australia in a limbo. One of our clients has to reschedule her parents travel due to the restriction of entry imposed by their own country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DAMA</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-sponsorship-visa-specialists-are-you-doing-the-right-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2019 22:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-sponsorship-visa-specialists-are-you-doing-the-right-way/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered if you have made a right decision about coming to Australian, and now you have to face another critical one how to stay here permanently after all failing in love stories, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t has to be only human contact but city and culture. Obviously the changing policy doesn&amp;rsquo;t help you in this regard, and even worse the continua negative updated migration news test your every nerves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The five year subclass 870 Sponsored Parent Visa </title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/fi-employer-sponsor-visa-specialists-be-in-the-best-position/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/fi-employer-sponsor-visa-specialists-be-in-the-best-position/</guid>
      <description>On 1 March 2019, Minister Coleman announced that applications to sponsor a parent for a Sponsored Parent (Temporary) visa will be open from 17 April 2019.
The visa provides parents with a new pathway to temporarily reunite with their children and grandchildren in Australia, while ensuring that taxpayers are not required to cover additional costs. The visa responds to community concerns about the limited number of Parent places in the migration program and associated lengthy waiting periods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visa 190 Victoria State Nominated Permanent Visa Opportunities for Cook, Baker, Interpreter, Chef, Human Resources Manager, Dietitian, etc...</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-sponsorship-visa-specialists-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 09:50:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-sponsorship-visa-specialists-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy/</guid>
      <description>Great news that VIC State government has updated the latest states nomination positions, and above listed occupations on the demanding. As every state government has certain cope number each year for occupations according to the Federal government immigration policy, we would suggest qualified candidates should arrange the state nomination ASAP to make yourself on the queue. Average estimated processing time for visa 190 is from 7 to 9 months. Most likely you are eligible to a Victoria State Skill Nominated Permanent Visa if you are working as :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FI Employer Sponsor Visa Specialists - Be in the best position</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/are-you-doing-the-right-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 10:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/are-you-doing-the-right-way/</guid>
      <description>If you do not have required working experience, the working visa can be considered as the pass way to Australian Permanent Residency. In other words, If you are a professionals, technicians and trades workers (accountant, soft engineer, nurse, cook, programmer developer and etc), the first step you should accumulate working experiences. the choices can be training visa or graduated visa, which usually allow the work in your file for up to 2 years depending on the occupation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FI Employer Sponsor Visa Specialists - What should I consider before hiring a Working Holiday Maker ?</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-visa-specialist-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 21:04:41 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-visa-specialist-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy/</guid>
      <description>What should I consider before hiring a Working Holiday Maker?
 Work should not be the main purpose of the visa-holder&amp;rsquo;s stay. Any work should be secondary to the main purpose of the stay — a holiday. The visa holder can only work with the same employer for a maximum of six months. The Working Holiday Maker may have extra visa conditions and a breach of any condition could result in the visa being cancelled and the visa holder having to leave Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finer Immigration Sponsorship Visa Specialists - Are you doing the right way</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-visa-specialist-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 09:50:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-visa-specialist-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy-1/</guid>
      <description>Your business can benefit from employing people from overseas if you need skills that are in short supply, or if you want to discover new ideas and technologies.
You can also employ workers who are living overseas but want to come work in Australia by either:
 Sponsoring a worker on a permanent basis: You can sponsor skilled workers for permanent migration through the Employer Nomination Scheme or the Regional Sponsored Migration Scheme (if your business is in regional Australia).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRANCAIS Contactez Nous</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/contact/_index.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 15:53:27 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/contact/_index.fr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FRANCAIS Portfolio</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/portfolio/_index.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 15:45:06 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/portfolio/_index.fr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A propos de nous ...</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/about/_index.fr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 12:37:52 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/about/_index.fr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>