<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Visa Specialists Blog on VISA Specialists | Finer Immigration</title>
    <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Visa Specialists Blog on VISA Specialists | Finer Immigration</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 12:23:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FI Employer Sponsor Visa Specialists - Be in the best position</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/are-you-doing-the-right-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 10:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/are-you-doing-the-right-way/</guid>
      <description>If you do not have required working experience, the working visa can be considered as the pass way to Australian Permanent Residency. In other words, If you are a professionals, technicians and trades workers (accountant, soft engineer, nurse, cook, programmer developer and etc), the first step you should accumulate working experiences. the choices can be training visa or graduated visa, which usually allow the work in your file for up to 2 years depending on the occupation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FI Employer Sponsor Visa Specialists - What should I consider before hiring a Working Holiday Maker ?</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-visa-specialist-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 21:04:41 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-visa-specialist-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy/</guid>
      <description>What should I consider before hiring a Working Holiday Maker?
 Work should not be the main purpose of the visa-holder&amp;rsquo;s stay. Any work should be secondary to the main purpose of the stay — a holiday. The visa holder can only work with the same employer for a maximum of six months. The Working Holiday Maker may have extra visa conditions and a breach of any condition could result in the visa being cancelled and the visa holder having to leave Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finer Immigration Sponsorship Visa Specialists - Are you doing the right way</title>
      <link>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-visa-specialist-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 09:50:00 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.finerimmigration.com.au/blog/finer-immigration-visa-specialist-are-you-doing-the-right-way-copy-1/</guid>
      <description>Your business can benefit from employing people from overseas if you need skills that are in short supply, or if you want to discover new ideas and technologies.
You can also employ workers who are living overseas but want to come work in Australia by either:
 Sponsoring a worker on a permanent basis: You can sponsor skilled workers for permanent migration through the Employer Nomination Scheme or the Regional Sponsored Migration Scheme (if your business is in regional Australia).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>